oldrepublic.net 2019-03-11

# Privacy Policy | Oldrepublic.NET

  * [Home](http://www.oldrepublic.net/) __
  * Privacy Policy

* * *

We respect the privacy of our users, and as a result the only personal information we collect is the one you choose to provide us with (such as when creating an account on our website, for example).

OLDREPUBLIC.NET does not sell, make public, rent, or share any personally identifiable information provided by our users with third-party entities or individuals outside our website staff and the companies that help us run it.

We may occasionally display advertisements from Google and other third-party vendors that rely on cookies to serve ads. These cookies are only used to collect various Internet usage statistics and preferences in order to serve more relevant ads.

OLDREPUBLIC.NET is not responsible for the content of external sites to which we link. Each website has their own terms of usage and privacy policies and we recommend you read them for each site you visit before providing them with any personal data.

We collect data from cookies since they allow us to recognize you each time you visit and personalize some of our site’s features to better suit your needs. Please keep in mind cookies do not contain any personal information.

While we do not share the personal information you provide us with, you are solely responsible for keeping your passwords and other account details secure.

Third-party websites and services accessible through OLDREPUBLIC.NET have their own privacy policies and terms of use for which we are not liable nor responsible. If you have any questions about their privacy policies, please contact these third-parties directly.
